Hello friends welcome to your
youtube3 Due to selling in the market,
we have seen that retailers are
selling in panic and there is a lack of buying in the
market, due to the same reason we are seeing stocks
falling and a fall was seen in the market
and if we talk about ICICI Lombard
stock, then
we have seen a fall of above 1 in the stock,
so after the market session closed, a
big update related to the stock has come,
due to which
we can see the impact of this news on the stock in Monday's trading session
and if the market
remains positive then
we can also see a positive impact on the stock,
so the news is that ICICI
Lombard General Insurance Company has
got a big relief in the tax matter
and on Friday the company informed that the
Income Tax Appeal Commissioner has given a
decision in favor of the company in the tax disputes going on in Mumbai, that is,
a case related to tax was to be heard against the company, for
which  In this regard, the
decision has come in favour of the company yesterday and
after this decision, the tax liability of ICICI Lombard which was around Rs 174 crore has
now been reduced and this relief has been given
in the tax matters of the business year i.e. from financial year 2012 to financial year 2017-18, that is, the
company had to
pay out tax of around Rs 174 crore related to all these financial years,
now the company has got relief
and the company informed that on January 9, 2025
at 5:43 pm,
a joint order has been issued by the Income Tax Appeal Commissioner 54 Mumbai
and this order has been given in the reference of the appeals filed by the company for the
financial years 2012 to 13, 15 to 16 and 16 to 17
and 17 to 18,
so if we
talk about the valuation of the stock, the
stock price is Rs 41.8 and the industry price is Rs 41.8.  It is
54.8, which means that
according to the valuation, the stock is trading at the right price
and due to the fall in the market,
we are getting the stock at a huge discount as
well and if we look at the
support of ICICI Lord stock, then
we can see the first support
at 1845 in the stock, the second
support can be seen at 816 in the stock,
so if we look at the resistance, there is
resistance at ₹1196 in the stock,
if the stock breaks the resistance
then we
can see a positive movement in the stock, the rest is
positive news for the company, the
company has got tax relief of 174 crores, from
which the company will get a lot of benefit,
so friends, if you have not subscribed to our channel yet,
then to
know the latest updates related to the share market,
please subscribe my channel and thank
you for watching this video and have a great
day guys